Woman, what's your name?
Do not be shy.
Tell me.
Wait!
I got you!
You are my prey!
How dare you?
Planning:
MASAO SATO
History:
MIKI NANBARA
Photography:
KIYOSHI KITASAKA
Screenplay:
Masahiro Shimura
SUZUKI NORIBUMI
Music:
Haru, Masahide Sakuma
Cast:
KYOKO TSUJISAWA
NOMURA MAMI
YUMI IORI
NATSUKO YAMAMOTO
YASUKO YAGAMI
HIROSHI KATSUNO
TERUHIKO AOI
SUZUKI NORIBUMI
DOLLS OF THE SHOGUN'S HAREM
The government of
Tokugawa Shogunate ...
... in Edo  ...
was stable with ...
fourth Shogun, Ietsuna.
Chiyoda is the Castle
symbol of its sovereignty.
There is  center
political control ...
the official residence ...
Shogun's ...
...  stays personal
and his private harem.
This is the entrance door.
Nobody except Shogun ...
can enter ...
Women's garden.
You got lucky.
Although born plebeian ...
... one day you can travel
in a luxurious palanquin.
Here.
Yajima Madam, what is that?
The palanquin of Anekouji.
Onatsu, sit down, please.
The greatest courtesan mistress
can go into the harem palanquin.
But that is going!
Once you reach this prestigious
mimen as you want.
High.
- Yajima, Onatsu this is?
- Yes, ma'am.
The staff took the servant
the Shogun, Ikegai Shinjuurou ...
... and has been educated with freight
Japanese to perform this task.
It seems that this girl
Cree is very important.
¡Onatsu, tilted his head!
Onatsu, we are the six
Shogun's favorite concubine.
Starting today,
so you'll be.
You will have to be modest,
not arrogant show ...
... and not to insult anyone on the court.
Of course.
Please llamadme Onatsu.
I'm new.
Nice to know.
Soy Okoto.
It is a pleasure.
My name is Oran.
Ofuji.
Okiku.
Omino.
I belong to a family
Kyoto aristocrat.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
According to the rules ...
... must take an oath.
As proof of your commitment,
have to sign ...
... this contract
us six witnesses.
It's the princess of the castle tanuki!
He introduced the Shogun!
My lord.
This will serve Onatsu
night in bed.
Onatsu ¿?
Found ...
... in the mountains the other day.
It was his capture.
This is to check whether
hide weapons in their hair.
Do not talk of politics in the bed.
Do not make personal applications.
Okiri be with you.
I will see and hear everything.
Morning report
to the veterans.
Forgive me.
The game moves me.
I was a savage.
- You are my prey.
- My lord.
Have a child.
Give me an heir.
"My lord, let me pregnant!"
That screaming like a beast.
You need discipline.
What did he?
Ran out of breath.
He said: "Onatsu, I'm your horse."
What does that mean?
Onatsu was above him.
I was riding.
Mounting ¿?
It was ingenious.
Women must be under the man.
Between all the people,
andalusia mounted Shogun!
Visit the Temple Jonen ¿?
I heard that helps women
to become pregnant.
You go there tomorrow.
- I can not.
- Why not?
Tomorrow I will visit the
my family cemetery.
I have permission.
You mean that
is more important?
- It is not that.
- No Tomorrow.
Someone else will.
Do not want to climb?
It's your chance to be
the mother of a Shogun.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
I'm going to the tea party.
Omino.
What you hurry?
Ven.
Lady.
Do not do that.
I am the concubine of the Shogun.
We should not do.
My fingers remember
each body part.
Even the most secret.
To love each
After that came from Kyoto.
The maids could be
home once in a while ...
... but not concubines.
had to stay in the castle.
The only exception
was to visit ...
their cemeteries ...
families once a year.
Doctor Genshiro Chujo "
Bend your knees.
Inhaled.
Exhale.
Again.
In three months.
Get rid of him.
Bite you.
When it comes together
a man and a woman ...
... is it that
has problems.
If you move, you die.
I do not understand.
You're a good doctor.
Why live here?
Because I like it.
I worked for Lord Hotta.
- Problems with a girl?
- No.
You are very passionate
Doctors should
to meet women.
It's true.
If I hire a lord ...
... could not save these girls.
Show me to abort babies.
I am a good mangante.
I'm good Mangado.
What is that?
- Dr.Chujo?
- Yes
Come with me.
Osumi was sick
en route to the cemetery.
- Osumi?
- Yes
Is at home with their parents.
Genshiro.
Been a long time.
Looks good, sir.
I've been busy since
our lord ...
... became chamberlain.
Too much work
to get sick.
Well, what happens?
Suddenly I felt bad.
But I'm better.
The Genshiro see you cured.
Friends were very small.
It has become ill
because he missed it.
Do not say that.
- I'll have to examine it.
- Thanks.
Túmbate.
Cold?
No.
Everything seems normal.
I'm not pretending.
I did not say otherwise.
But ...
it is true that you ...
I missed a lot.
I am pleased.
Do not be so.
Your mother is ...
... on the way home.
Be good o. ..
... the sea is agitated.
Lady.
Thanks for helping.
It's nothing.
How does it feel?
Much better now.
Still no time to lose.
Go home and see your parents.
Yes, thanks.
Come back in two hours.
Do you work in the harem?
His parents sold fans.
The maids can
leave every 6 months.
The envy.
You can enjoy life.
But a concubine ...
neither is free ...
and enjoys the love.
"The leader of a country should
leading to his first family. "
"The leader of a family
disciplining itself. "
"To be self -
must be strong-minded. "
I'm the fourth Shogun
Tokugawa regime.
Who will be my heir?
What have you done?
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Do not touch it!
It's the Shogun's underwear!
What is your name?
Yoshino.
I deal with the bathroom.
Sorry.
Yoshino ¡!
What have you done?
The Shogun's underwear!
Omatsu, you're the greatest girl.
- How will the punishment?
- Sorry.
With not enough!
¡Córtate hair in repentance!
Deserve severe punishment.
He presents You!
He introduced the Shogun!
What has he done?
Has been neglected ...
... and has caused this disaster.
It has also damaged
their underwear, sir.
The severely punished.
According to the rules ...
Will be expelled.
My lord.
It was not the fault of anyone.
Dry your.
Castiguéis not.
Understood?
We'll show you ...
... a fascinating game of women.
- A women's game?
- Yes
The game of the rope!
¡The winners will reward!
Strive to the maximum.
¡Throw the rope and pray ...
... for the blessing of the birth!
¡Prepare!
Get Started!
Win! White!
Great!
Drink! All!
¡Llenaos tonight!
My lord.
Thank you.
I will never forget ...
... your kindness.
Comes Your Honor!
Omino, are you pregnant?
Doctor informs the Shogun.
Yes
Is three months.
¡Omino, get it!
Take care much ...
... and have a healthy baby.
Yes
Thank you very much, sir.
That is a child.
Will be the next Shogun's mother.
The Chamberlain could not Hotta
better to have found an heir.
Keep your position,
Sakai minister.
For a long time.
Sakai-Anekoji the team ...
... serve the next Shogun.
He introduced Chamberlain Hotta!
Omino, who is the father?
What?
Show respect for
the son of the Shogun!
Enough!
He asked Omino.
Omino, you can not deceive me.
I have spies outside the castle.
In March ...
... visited the Temple Jonen.
What happened there?
Dímelo o. ..
... I will ask the priest.
Yesterday he told the judge ...
Omino ... how he has deceived.
He has confessed everything!
Is that true?
What have you done?
Sorry!
Beware of fire!
Omino.
Is it true what the priest?
You're a concubine of the Shogun.
How could you do?
You're hiding something.
Omino, tell the truth ...
... or get tortured to death.
Mrs Anekoji planned it.
What?
Deny your request
to visit the temple.
Perhaps the Shogun is sterile.
But I want you
getting pregnant.
If sterile
How I will do?
Do not you know?
We had planned to Osumi ...
... but perhaps you're better ...
... because you keep a secret.
Do not worry.
I've prepared everything.
The next day I went to ...
Temple Jonen  ... as I said.
I could have happened to me.
Fell into the trap in my place.
Sorry.
Nothing happens.
Mrs Anekoji is terrible.
Pretended to know nothing.
Osumi.
Please do not tell.
Why?
I can not live.
He betrayed Mrs Anekoji.
Come on.
But ...
Hide somewhere
party tonight.
Tomorrow I will tell
to the veterans.
Come on.
Who are you?
Keep your mouth shut.
How could you?
Osumi, is one of the rules.
Like this.
Now you're also guilty.
Somebody!
- Intruder!
- Seize him!
¡Intruders!
Intrusive.
- Omino!
- Leave me here!
Omino, come on.
Go, Osumi!
Leave me here.
Do not give up!
Thanks!
I am satisfied.
You do well.
Omino.
Omino ¡!
Come, follow me.
You can escape here.
Thanks, Yoshino.
Osumi ¡!
Genshiro.
What happened?
Something terrible.
He fled the harem.
What?
Come on.
Are you hurt?
After what has happened ...
... I can not go back to my parents.
I could have committed suicide ...
... but wanted to see again.
Osumi.
That's it.
Now I do not die.
Do not say that.
You need to dry clothes.
Welcome.
- Are you my daughter?
- No, sir.
Why you ask?
A messenger of the harem.
Osumi has escaped.
No!
I have to punish with death ...
... to save our honor.
She understands.
Genshiro.
She loves you.
You can come here.
If the support ...
... will be punished too.
Do me a favor.
Kill it and defend my honor.
Entiérrala anywhere.
But not in our cemetery.
I brought some money.
Use it to your
soul rest in peace.
I was stupid.
I thought that serving the Shogun ...
... in bed, I am honored.
The father and daughter ...
Two stupid.
What a dumb way to secede.
Since the sudden
Omino death ...
... the Shogun is sick.
You can die in
any time.
We must ask you
make a decision.
The best thing would be to accept
Tsunayoshi Lord ...
... as an heir to the castle.
I agree.
Tsunayoshi Lord is his brother.
There is no better successor.
Silence!
The Shogun has no children ...
... and that is worrying.
But it is too early to
say it is sterile.
We can not wait to check.
That is an insult to him.
What happens if you have a child before that
Tsunayoshi becomes heir?
What else?
There would be a great confusion.
We present the Shogun.
Another reunion for
choose my successor?
Yes, my lord.
We turn.
Stay at the harem, please.
I do not need your instructions.
I am not a stud!
The ship returns to home ...
... with your mother on board.
As a gift, will bring ...
... a red dress and a belt.
So it is good and sleeps well ...
... or shake the sea.
Your mother is ...
... on the way home.
Beautiful song.
Let me hear more.
I've come to the heart.
I may not look.
- Excuse me.
- Okay. Alzate.
You have very soft eyes.
You name?
Yoshino.
Yoshino ¿?
Nice name.
My lord!
Sorry.
Nothing happens.
My servants should
be laughing at me.
I am lewd, passionate ...
... idiot and a madman.
No!
I know that is nice.
I will never forget their generosity.
The other day estropeé
their underwear.
I was punished, but ...
... you saved me from the worst.
I was the servant
to which helped.
His smile is gracious
etched in my head.
His voice still resonates in my ears.
His continued support me.
You are very sincere.
I'm surprised you live ...
... in this nest of foxes.
My lord!
Yoshino.
My lord.
I do not deserve your love.
Yoshino.
Glad ...
... to have.
The pleasure is mine.
I am happy.
Yoshino.
Sálvame.
Two months later  ...
...  the Shogun had Ietsuna
a heart attack and died.
The Shogun is dead!
It's over!
His sudden death
caused an uproar.
When appointing
A new Shogun ...
... except  veterans ...
... all the ladies were released.
The Shogun's concubines
became nuns ...
... and lived in the stronghold
outside the castle ...
during the mourning ...
rest of their lives.
- Onatsu late. Traedla.
- Yes
Onatsu not wearing the
appropriate attire.
Get dressed in white.
No!
I stay in the harem.
Why should I become a nun?
I am sure that
gustaré the new Shogun.
Shut up!
Are you crazy?
- Córtate hair!
- No. No!
His stay in the
harem came to an end.
Ladies and courtesans
left the castle.
The maids could return
home with their relatives.
He introduced the new Shogun!
few days later, the new
Shogun came to the castle.
was appointed by his brother.
It was the fifth Shogun
Tokugawa regime.
Is here.
Genshiro.
What do you want, chamberlain?
I have a job for you.
No one else can.
Find a woman.
Your talents will be useful to us.
- A woman special?
- Yes
A concubine of the Shogun.
I heard one of them
she became pregnant.
It would be a problem.
Against the wishes of Sakai ...
Tsunayoshi has ...
become Shogun.
Sakai not keep silent.
If you find that the deceased
Shogun had a baby ...
... it will appoint an heir.
This would recover his position.
To avoid disturbances ...
... we must not give him the chance.
Want to find ...
... abortion to women and the baby?
Genshiro do it for us.
You'll have a great reward ...
... and a place in the clan.
I do not want neither money nor a job.
- Do you refuse?
- I like my life.
The skirmishes for power
Case you are ...
... not mine.
Shut up!
We know that to hide
the concubine who escaped.
Reconsidéralo.
If you refuse,
¡Be arrested!
We have a clue.
The late Shogun we talked about it.
It is a very special woman.
When you love ...
... smell of musk.
A woman almizcleña.
How is that?
The smell coming from parts
when in ecstasy.
- Try the five nuns?
- Yes
It is an exceptional occasion.
It is unusual to try
the concubines of the Shogun.
"Sakurada Mansion"
Comes Your Honor!
Shut up, please!
Soy Onatsu, the most
beloved by the Shogun.
Make me yours.
Let's make love, sir!
Poor woman!
It's crazy ...
... who died from the Shogun.
No doubt.
Loved more than any.
We will be here forever.
I too crazy again.
Madam, the doctor arrived.
The cause is suffering.
Let alone the review.
If you need something, contact me.
Let me see.
Okay.
My lord, I have been waiting for.
My lord.
What a shame. That is armatoste
all you have to get?
Shut up!
Try my legendary sword
and compare with this piece.
For your good will
better not look.
You're wet!
That saves time.
Still.
Freeze!
- But you move.
- Not you!
Do not be afraid, dear.
You are the following.
Ok.
I see.
You're not pregnant.
My lord.
A woman almizcleña.
Have you heard anything about that?
Do not stop!
There, stand there!
OK, but why not.
And here?
I do not care.
I do not care!
Welcome.
- Are you still awake?
- Yes
Sorry, too late.
Genshiro, are you awake?
Yes
I do not hide anything, right?
No, nothing.
Do not do anything dangerous.
I do not know what he would do without you.
What will become of me if I do not come back?
Stay together.
Where is Jakko?
Has to pee.
How vulgar!
The Zuimyo sister is back!
Come on, move!
- Zuimyo, what happens?
- Sister Zuimyo. The door!
Open the door!
Osumi ¡!
"We have your wife."
"If you want to return,
Sakurada to see the mansion. "
Master.
The concubines of the Shogun ...
... here are confined.
Why do not you?
What is this?
- Entregadme average.
- You are not what they seek.
We want to Genshiro.
Genshiro not responsible.
Chamberlain works for Hotta.
Is looking to partner ...
... pregnant.
Why do you accept?
For your freedom, huh?
Here it is.
Genshiro.
¡Genshiro, do not worry about me!
Welcome, Genshiro.
I have come.
Soltadla.
First pull your sword.
¡Tírala!
¡Matadle!
I must do something.
Shogun will go to the bedroom.
Where are my audience?
Did not you hear me?
¡Take me there!
Fire! Fire!
Fire!
Turn off the fire!
The harem is burning!
- Plant.
- Yes
- Use this.
Does it hurt?
That was true of only
The injured includes pain.
Sorry.
You did for me.
No!
I want to return to the past.
Are we back to the past?
You are here ... alive.
With that I am worth.
Genshiro.
If you have forgiven me ...
... Would you marry me?
As lovers.
As before.
Osumi.
Onatsu.
Onatsu ¿?
How long.
Is this really you, Onatsu?
Now my name is Aoi Dayu.
It has become crazy.
I am afraid I must leave the house.
The influential gentlemen Owari
Date and are near here.
We'll see.
Now I make Oiram.
What?
- No smell of musk?
- No.
The test for all and nothing.
I doubt that the deceased
Shogun had a son.
Should be outside the harem.
What are you afraid?
Even if true,
Who can prove it?
- There is a test.
- Huh?
Before dying ...
... gave a certificate to the woman.
A certificate?
"Pilgrimage to the Temple Asakusa
Asakusa is one of the
festivals of the harem.
It is an imitation of
Asakusa festival .
The ladies wearing masks
and enjoy the evening.
Who are you?
Miya ¿?
What are you doing?
I do not like the festival.
How dare you?
Estate and still not hurt you.
I will take you to heaven.
Stop!
I're insulting!
Tell me who smells like musk.
The Shogun left pregnant.
I do not know.
Faster!
- Who is it?
- I do not know.
Tell me who he is.
Yoshino.
- Yoshino?
- Yes
He left the castle.
I do not know where.
¿Yoshino is a certificate?
- I do not know.
- You have to know.
No!
Let her!
So this is the certificate.
Sorry!
Excuse me!
What? Do not know how
contact your parents?
That will make it difficult for the wedding.
I commiserate of Yoshino.
At last he had said ...
You may be at home.
Yoshino is not true
daughter of Fushimiya.
What?
His mother was a poor servant.
Should have deambulado
Yoshino since birth.
He was found half
dead by Fushimiya.
They tried to help,
but it was impossible.
They had no children of their own,
so I adopted it.
So we have no clue?
Wait! Yoshino always
sing the same lullaby.
I doubt that it will serve, but
may be a clue.
What, Kanji?
I know that I have heard before
somewhere.
Really?
That's right!
Now I remember!
A woman in the red district
Benten-cho used to sing.
The newly Wakasa sell!
Wakasa ¿?
A lullaby of Wakasa.
Is your mother there?
Yoshino.
Yoshino ¿?
Hey, is not pregnant.
Where is your baby?
What baby?
We know that the Shogun
let you pregnant.
No.
Is a child.
The son of the late Shogun?
No!
I have proof.
The Shogun wrote this
certificate for you.
It has nothing to do with my son.
Who is the father?
It's just me ...
... and my first love.
- Are you worth it?
- No.
The Shogun's son must die.
No, Genshiro!
Osumi, what are you doing?
I am concerned about it.
- Please forgive.
- I can not.
Osumi.
Please!
Do not kill the child!
Osumi.
- I buy your freedom.
- I do not care.
¡Forgive them, please!
I heard the story of the nanny.
A woman was sold ...
... to a brothel, leaving a baby.
Joanna fewer ...
... escaped.
Remo in a boat
half of the storm.
He had no supplies.
I had no money.
In the end he could not see the baby.
The waves swallowed
the unhappy mother.
All mothers love their children.
Genshiro, understand, please.
"Yoshino's son added."
"Ietsuna Shogun."
Genshiro.
Master.
Master!
Is this OK?
My job is to perform abortions.
Like give me the imperial children.
'll Reason.
Sorry, but I must interrupt.
It's something personal.
The truth is that ...
What?
I'm going to have my own kid!
It must be the end of the world!
This is a signal.
When I look to the sea and, for me
believe that the Shogun's harem there.
If you think about it, there.
If not, cease to exist.
Yoshino has brought us this far.
So that we can be happy.
harem beauties and 3,000 ...
existed only for ...
the pleasure of a man.
But the bells
stopped ringing ...
...  two centuries later.
Translated by: Fingolfin
www.allzine.org